 [{
         "movieQuestion": "What’s the name of the skyscraper in Die Hard?",
         "answers": ["Nakatomi Plaza", "Nakatomi Tower", "Nakatomi Building", "Nakatomi Place"],
         "correctAnswer": "Nakatomi Plaza"
     },

     {
         "movieQuestion": "In which of his movies does Robert De Niro famously say “You talkin’ to me?”",
         "answers": ["Scar Face", "Taxi Driver", "Raging Bull", "Goodfellas"],
         "correctAnswer": "Taxi Driver"

     },

     {
         "movieQuestion": "Which award winning director plays Korg in Thor: Ragnarok",
         "answers": ["Tim Burton", "J. J. Abrams", "Taika Waititi", "Anthony Rosso"],
         "correctAnswer": "Taika Waititi"

     },

     {
         "movieQuestion": "Who is the only actor to receive an Oscar nomination for acting in a Lord of the Rings movie?",
         "answers": ["Elijah Wood", "Ian McKellen", "Andy Serkis", "Hugo Weaving"],
         "correctAnswer": "Ian McKellen"

     },

     {
         "movieQuestion": "What song plays over the opening credits of Guardians of the Galaxy?",
         "answers": ["Come and Get Your Love", "Fox on the Run", "Oooh Child", "Hooked on a Feeling"],
         "correctAnswer": "Come and Get Your Love"

     },

     {
         "movieQuestion": "Which Harry Potter star will be playing the dark knight in Matt Reeves upcoming movie 'The Batman'?",
         "answers": ["Tom Felton", "Daniel Radcliffe", "Matthew Lewis", "Robert Pattinson"],
         "correctAnswer": "Robert Pattinson"

     },

     {
         "movieQuestion": "What is the highest-grossing movie of all time (not adjusted for inflation)?",
         "answers": ["Titanic", "Avatar", "Avengers Endgame", "Star Wars V"],
         "correctAnswer": "Avengers Endgame"

     },

     {
         "movieQuestion": "For which one of these movies did Margot Robbie receive an oscar nomination?",
         "answers": ["Wolf of Wall Street", "I, Tonya", "Suicide Squad", "Once Upon A Time In Hollywood"],
         "correctAnswer": "I, Tonya"

     },

     {
         "movieQuestion": "What was Quentin Tarantino‘s first feature as writer/director?",
         "answers": ["Jackie Brown", "Reservoir Dogs", "Pulp Fiction", "From Dusk Till Dawn"],
         "correctAnswer": "Reservoir Dogs"

     },

     {
         "movieQuestion": "Which one of these Tim Burton films did composer Danny Elfman voice a character?",
         "answers": ["Bettle Juice", "Nightmare Before Christmas", "Planet of the Apes", "Frankenweenie"],
         "correctAnswer": "Nightmare Before Christmas"

     }
 ]

